好的，你已经完成了
All right, you're done.
看一下现在的情况
Let's take a look at the solution.
增加了对插入位置的支持，看起来就像
Adding support for the location
insert looks almost identical
增加了对weather的支持一样
to adding the support for weather.
我们只需要选择正确的表名，然后返回一个正确的位置URI
We just have to select the right table
name, and return the right location URI.
记住，在函数的最后，我们要调用getcontentresolver里的notifychange这个函数
Remember, at the end of the function,
we can just call notify change on
去通知所有的注册的观察者
the content resolver to notify
all of the registered observers.
注意到我们必须使用URI路径而不是返回URI
Note that we must use the past in URI,
and not the return URI,
因为它不会正确的通知我们游标的变化
as that will not correctly notify
our cursors of the change.
由于我们取消了testInsertreadProvider函数的注释
Since we also uncommented
test insert read provider,
让我们运行一下测试，确保一切都是可以用的
lets run our test just to make sure
everything's still working well.
没有什么错误显示在设备的屏幕上
Note that nothing appears
on device screen.
嗯，我们的测试通过了
And, our test passed.
我们在content provider的道路上越走越顺了
We're well on our way to
building our content provider.